A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Economic Opportunity and Assets Program, Quality Employment Unit, Office Files of Helen Neuborne FA1837
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation records, Economic Opportunity and Assets Program, Quality Employment Unit, Office Files of Helen Neuborne
1974-2015
Rockefeller Archive Center
Ford Foundation
Neuborne, Helen
FA1837
15.19 Cubic Feet 40 letter size document boxes.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Ford Foundation archive was deposited at the RAC in 2011. Ford Foundation records, correspondence, reports, program files, and officers' papers were transferred to and accessioned by the RAC beginning in 2011.
This material was transferred to the RAC in 2021 and was ingested by the RAC as Accession 2021:015.
Accessions continue as necessary.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Arrangement
Collection consists of one series.
Collection arrangement is as follows:
Series 1. Subject files, 1974-2015
Scope and Contents
Collection contains the files Helen Neuborne created during her support and leadership of the Ford Foundation's programming for expanding economic opportunity and assets building. Most of the collection's contents originate from Neuborne's career at the Ford Foundation between 2003 and 2016 when she served as Senior Program Officer in the Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit and then as Director of the Quality Employment unit in the later Economic Opportunity and Assets Program. Neuborne had previous positions in the Foundation's programs for human rights and reproductive health, but there is only a small number of materials documenting that work included within the collection.
The collection is comprised of one series of subject files. These files document Neuborne's responsibilities for grants management and program strategy. Neuborne and her respective program units oversaw grants in support of low-wage workers in relation to access to public benefits, workforce development, state and Federal labor market policy, fair wages, the balance between work and family, and the intersection of employment and economic status with gender, race, disability, and immigration status. In regards to program strategy, several files in the collection pertain to the Ford Foundation's program restructuring when Luis Ubinas became President. There are materials documenting the development of Lines of Work statements.
Common material formats found throughout the collection include correspondence, notes, notebooks, drafts, grant proposals, grant recommendations, reports, graphs and tables, meeting materials, news articles, and publications. There are also digital media items in the collection and one photograph which shows Neuborne.
Ford Foundation; Economic policy; Employment -- United States; Foreign workers--United States; Labor policy; Minimum wage; Parental leave; Public welfare; Sick leave; Tax Credits--United States; UnEmployment insurance--United States; Women -- Employment; Women's rights; Work and family; Working class families--United States--Economic conditions; Working poor
- Subject files, 1974-2015; 1; 15.19 Cubic Feet 40 letter size document boxes.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains subject files Helen Neuborne created and maintained when she served as Senior Program Officer of the Ford Foundation's Asset Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) Economic Development unit and then as Director of the Quality Employment unit in the Foundation's Economic Opportunity and Assets Program.
  Files in the series pertaining to Neuborne's grants management responsibilities show the Ford Foundation's programming interest in creating a more inclusive economy and promoting economic development and asset building among working class families. Different areas of focus documented include:
  - Securing access to public benefits for low-wage workers, the U.S. Federal Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC), paid sick days and family leave, and the role of employers in ensuring their employees access public benefits - Federal and state labor market, welfare, and economic policy with particular focus on the George W. Bush administration, the Barack Obama administration, and policy directed towards economic recovery after the 2008 Gobal Financial Crisis - Workforce development for low-wage workers and demonstration projects dedicated to this - Fair wages and raising the minimum wage - The balance between work and family and work flexibility - Families and children in relation to economic status and poverty - Women in the workforce and the intersection of employment and economic status with gender, race, disability, and immigration status
  Grantee organizations and collaborative partners include the Families and Work Institute (FWI), MDRC, the Annie E. Casey Foundation (AECF), the Grantmakers Income Security Taskforce (GIST), the National Employment Law Project (NELP), the Center on Budget and Policy Priorities (CBPP), the Urban Institute, and Seedco.
  Files related to Neuborne's support and leadership of her units' program strategy efforts contain program officer and reflection memos, materials concerning Ford Foundation organizational meetings and meetings with Foundation Trustees, and materials documenting the Foundation's program restructuring when Luis Ubinas became President. Many of the program reorganization records show the development of Lines of Work statements.
  There is also a small group of materials in the series Neuborne created when she worked in the Foundation's programs for human rights and reproductive health from the late 1990s to the early 2000s.
  Common material formats found throughout the series include correspondence, notes, drafts, grant proposals, grant recommendations, reports, graphs and tables, meeting materials like agendas, news articles, and publications. Notes Neuborne wrote are found throughout the series. They are included in various files and also appear in notebooks Neuborne maintained. Her notebooks appear to pertain to particular Ford Foundation colleagues and offices. In instances where the subjects of the notebooks are not described in the file title, scope and content notes have been added to the file to list the subjects. There are also digital media items in the series and one photograph which shows Neuborne.
  Files show Neuborne's frequent collaboration with Ford Foundation colleagues Anna Wadia, Chauncey Lennon, Hector Cordero-Guzman, and Pablo Farias.
  - Working Poor Families Project (WPFP), 2009 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Working Poor Families Project (WPFP) - Workplans, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Working Poor Families Project (WPFP) - Brandon Roberts, 2004-2005 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Working Poor Families Project (WPFP) - Brandon Roberts correspondence, 2003-2004 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Working Poor Families Project (WPFP) - Brandon Roberts, 2006-2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Worker centers and labor, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - National Employment Law Project (NELP) - Unemployment Insurance Safety Project, 2001-2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Urban Institute - The New Unemployment Project, 2010-2011 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Urban Institute, 2005-2007 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - University of Kentucky flexibility study, 2006-2007 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Barry L. Van Lare - Management and public policy consultant, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Violence Against Women Act (VAWA), 2009 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Washington Area Women's Foundation, 2003-2005 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - White House Luncheon - National Children' Hospital of Iraq, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Women In Informal Employment: Globalizing and Organizing (WIEGO), 2000-2004 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
  - Women In Informal Employment: Globalizing and Organizing (WIEGO), 2007-2009 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Women in Informal Employment: Globalizing and Organizing (WIEGO), 2004-2008 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Women in Informal Employment: Globalizing and Organizing (WIEGO), 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Changing the Povery Debate, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 20-23)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Maryland, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Massachusetts, 2003-2008 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Michigan, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Minnesota, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Mississippi, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Working Poor Families Project - New Mexico, 2005-2006 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Working Poor Families Project - New York, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Working Poor Families Project - North Carolina, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Ohio, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Oregon, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Pennsylvania, 2004-2007 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Washington, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Working Poor Families Project - Wisconsin Report, 2003-2006 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Working Poor Families Projects - Media coverage, 2004-2006 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Work Support Strategies - National Kick Off Conference, Washington D.C., 2011 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth, and Families (GCYF) Annual Conference, Atlanta Georgia, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth, and Families (GCYF) Annual Conference, Atlanta, Georgia, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Grantmakers for Children, Youth, and Families (GCYF) - Grantmakers in Health (GIH), 2007 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Living Cities, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Living Cities, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Living Cities, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 44-45)
  - Paid sick days, 2006-2007 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Paid sick days - Learning and funders, 2007 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Administration for Children and Families Office of Planning, Research, and Evaluation (OPRE) Technical Working Group Meeting, Washington D.C., 2012 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Administration for Children and Families Office of Planning, Research, and Evaluation (OPRE) Technical Working Group Meeting, Washington D.C., 2012 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Notebook - Pablo Farias, 2010-2011 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Connecting Lower Wage Employees to Governmental and Community Benefits, Supports, and Services, 2005 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Carsey Institute, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Jody Heymann - McGill University and Harvard University Press, 2003-2010 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Call to Renewal, 2003-2005 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - International Labour Organization (ILO) - Social protection, 2014 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted – Open in 2025
  - International Labour Organization (ILO) - Group of Friends led by the Swedish Prime Minister, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    Restricted – Open in 2026
  - Margaret Levi - Stanford University Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (CASBS) Project on Future of Work and Workers, 2015 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - Center for American Progress (CAP) - Economists, 2011 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Welfare policy and employment, 2001-2012 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - American Institute For Social Justice (AISJ) - Association of Community Organizations for Reform Now (ACORN), 2000-2010 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Notebooks, circa 2010-2015 (Box 7, Folder 61-64)
    Notebook subjects include: - Darren Walker - Pablo Farias - Anna Wadia - Vice President - Vice President - Unit - Unit - Laine Romero-Alston - Hector Cordero-Guzman - Vice President - Anna Wadia - Unit
  - Notebooks, circa 2013-2014 (Box 8, Folder 65-66)
    Notebooks subjects include: - Unit - Anna Wadia - Chuancy Lennon - Laine Romero-Alston
  - John Hoffmire - Staples and HR Block, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - John Hoffmire - University of Wisconsin-Madison Center on Business and Poverty, 2006-2008 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Human Services Coalition of Dade County - Prosperity Campaign and Imagine Miami, 2003-2006 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Human Services Coalition of Dade County, 2006-2007 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Roberta Iverson - Model Firms research, 2007-2008 (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research (IWPR), 2000-2002 (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Institute for Women's Policy Research (IWPR) - Paid sick leave, 2001-2005 (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Tom Kochan, Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) - Jobs Crisis Project, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 74)
  - George Lakoff, The Rockridge Institute, 2003-2004 (Box 9, Folder 75)
  - Jodi Levin-Epstein, Center for Law and Social Policy (CLASP) - Paid leave, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 76)
  - Legal Momentum, 1999-2005 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    The organization Legal Momentum was formerly called NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund.
  - Center for Economic and Policy Research (CEPR) - Bridging the Gaps Project, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 78)
  - Employers convening - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 79)
  - Employers convening - Ami Nagle consultant, Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC) Funders Network, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 80)
  - Employers convening - Notes, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 81)
  - Employers convening - Brookings Institution, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 82)
  - Employers convening - Center for Economic Progress (CEP), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 83)
  - Employers convening - Center for Law and Social Policy (CLASP) and report to Mott Foundation, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 84)
  - Employers convening - Corporate Voices for Working Families (CVWF), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 85)
  - Employers convening - CVS Pharmacy, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 86)
  - Employers convening - Center for Workforce Prep (CWP), 2005 (Box 9, Folder 87)
  - Employers convening - Denver, Colorado, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 88)
  - Employers convening - Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC) Funders Network, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 89)
  - Employers convening - Mark Greenberg, Center for Law and Social Policy (CLASP), 2005 (Box 10, Folder 90)
  - Employers convening - John Hoffmire, University of Wisconsin-Madison Center on Business and Poverty, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 91)
  - Employers convening - Families and Work Institute (FWI) and July 2005 Ford Foundation Meeting (Box 10, Folder 92)
  - Employers convening - HR Block, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 93)
  - Employers convening - Theresa Feeley, SF Works, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 94)
  - Employers convening - Seedco, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 95)
  - Employers convening - Seton Hall University and Mott Foundation, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Folder 96)
  - Employers convening - University of Wisconsin-Madison Center on Business and Poverty, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 97)
  - Employers convening - Brandee McHale's June 2005 Ford Foundation convening (Box 10, Folder 98)
  - Employers convening - Other donors, circa 2005 (Box 10, Folder 99)
  - Employers convening - Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC) Funders Network, circa 2005 (Box 10, Folder 100)
  - Employer group 2006 - Families and Work Institute (FWI), 2005 (Box 10, Folder 101)
  - Employer group 2006 - Employee assistance programs (EAPS) and work life, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 102)
  - Employer group 2006, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Employer group 2006 - Connecting Lower-Wage Employees to Governmental and Community Benefits, Supports, and Services: Innovations in the Private Sector, October 28, 2005 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Employer group 2006, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Employer group 2006 - Michele Kahane - Part of the Solution: Leveraging Business and Markets for Low-Income People, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Employer group 2006 - HR Block, 2004-2006 (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Employer group 2006, 2005 (Box 11, Folder 108)
  - Ford Foundation Joint Worldwide Meeting, San Francisco, California, October-November 2002 - Briefing Book (Box 11, Folder 109)
  - Ford Foundation Joint Worldwide Meeting, San Francisco, California, October-November 2002 - Faces of the Ford Foundation Family (Box 11, Folder 110)
  - Work Supports Strategies: Phase II National Kick-off Conference, Washington D.C., 2012 (Box 11, Folder 111)
  - Center for Economic and Policy Research (CEPR), 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 112)
  - Center for Economic and Policy Research (CEPR), 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 113)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives (CPA) - Workforce Investments Leadership Circle, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 114)
  - Center for Women and Work (CWW), 2005 (Box 11, Folder 115)
  - Community Benefits Initiative, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 116)
  - Annie E. Casey Foundation (AECF) Workforce Narrative Meeting, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 117)
  - Center for American Progress (CAP), 2015 (Box 11, Folder 118)
  - MDRC - Earned Income Tax Credit (EITC), 2014-2015 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - Hilary Pennington - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) The Second Machine Age Conference, 2014 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - Arkansas Career Pathways Initiative (CIP) and College Counts, 2008-2015 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - The American Prospect, 2000-2006 (Box 12, Folder 122)
  - SingleStop USA (SSUSA), 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 123)
  - Tony Sheldon - Social protection, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 124)
  - Social protection - Institute of Developmental Studies workshop, Sussex, England, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 125)
  - Service Employees International Union (SEIU), 2009 (Box 12, Folder 126)
  - SF Works, 2006-2007 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Southern Institute on Children and Families (SICF), 1995-2007 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Southern Business Leadership Council (SBLC), 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Southern Institute on Children and Families (SICF), 1995-2004 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - USAction, 2010-2011 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - United Way of America and One Economy Corporation, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - National Academy of Social Insurance (NASI), 2004 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - National Employment Law Project (NELP), 2009 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - National Employment Law Project (NELP), 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - National Governors' Association (NGA), 2010 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - National League of Cities Institute (NLCI), 2005-2006 (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - National Fund for Workforce Solutions (NFWS) Workforce Learning Solutions (WLS), 2012 (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - National Organization on Disability (NOD) - Army Wounded Warriors Project (AW2), 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - National Organization on Disability (NOD) - Army Wounded Warriors Project (AW2), 1982-2010 (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - National Partnership for Women and Families (NPWF) - Family and Medical Leave Act (FMLA), 2006-2007 (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - National Skills Coalition (NSC) meetings, 2009-2012 (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - National Skills Coalition (NSC) projects, 2013-2014 (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - National Urban League (NUL), 2009-2011 (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - New York City Conditional Cash Transfers (CCT), 2006-2008 (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - New York City Center for Economic Opportunity (CEO) - Veronica White, 2007-2009 (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - Orientation on community, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - National Partnership for Women and Families (NPWF) Paid Sick Days Summit, Washington D.C., 2010 (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - House hearings - Paid sick days, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Passion for Change documentary, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - Women Employed Institute, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - The Workforce Alliance (TWA), 2006-2008 (Box 14, Folder 152-153)
  - The Workforce Alliance Training Policy in Brief, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 153)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - The Workforce Alliance in the News, 2006-2007, circa 2007 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Working Families Coalition - Paid Leave Consortium, 2004 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Workers Defense Project (WDP), 2009-2012 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Ford Foundation sexuality and reproductive health, 1998-2001 (Box 15, Folder 156-157)
  - Ford Foundation Assets Building and Community Development Program (ASSETS) meetings, 1998-2001 (Box 15, Folder 158-159)
  - Notebook - Family Values at Work, July 22-24, undated (Box 15, Folder 160)
  - A Review of the Women's Funding Movement by Susan Davis and William B. Hart, 1991 September (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - Women's Program Forum (WPF), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 162-163)
  - Ford Foundation Assets Lines of Work Program Statements, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 164)
  - Ford Foundation Trustees - Quality Employment, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 165)
  - Northern California Ford Foundation Trustees visit, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 166)
  - Experts, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 167)
  - Ford Foundation Assets Lines of Work, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 168)
  - Other funders, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 169)
  - Lines of Work statements - Program Officer memos, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 170)
  - Affinity Group on Development Finance (AGDF) Social Protection Committee, 2006 (Box 16, Folder 171)
  - Pablo Farias - Assets, circa 2003-2007 (Box 16, Folder 172)
  - Social protection - Notes, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 173)
  - Social protection - Informal sector, global colleagues, 2007-2008 (Box 16, Folder 174)
  - Social protection, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 175)
  - Social protection - Women in Informal Employment: Globalizing and Organizing (WIEGO), 2008 (Box 16, Folder 176)
  - Reorganization - Lines of Work, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 177)
  - Reorganization - Lines of Work, 2008-2009 (Box 17, Folder 178)
  - Reorganization - John Colborn guidelines, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 179)
  - Reorganization - Next stages, undated (Box 17, Folder 180)
  - Reorganization - Final Lines of Work, undated (Box 17, Folder 181)
  - Reorganization - Lines of Work Section C, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 182)
  - Reorganization - Hector Cordero-Guzman correspondence, 2008 December (Box 17, Folder 183)
  - Supporting Work Project (SWP) and Federal policy opportunities, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 184)
  - Pablo Farias weekly, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 185)
  - Pablo Farias quarterly, 2009 (Box 17, Folder 186)
  - Workforce and work supports, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 187)
  - Workforce and work supports - Workforce policy initiative, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 188)
  - Workforce and work supports - Frank DeGiovanni and Pablo Farias notes, 2007-2008 (Box 17, Folder 189)
  - Workforce and work supports, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 190)
  - Workforce and work supports - Top 40 Ford Foundation Grant Recipients for Workforce Supports, 1936-Present, undated (Box 17, Folder 191)
  - Workforce and work supports - Active states, 2008 (Box 17, Folder 192)
  - Anna Wadia, 2008-2010 (Box 17, Folder 193)
  - Anna Wadia - Minimum wage, 2009-2010 (Box 17, Folder 194)
  - Anna Wadia - National Employment Law Project (NELP), 2008-2010 (Box 18, Folder 195)
  - Anna Wadia - Unemployment insurance, 2009-2010 (Box 18, Folder 196)
  - Anna Wadia - Building the Power of Women of Color to Change Public Policy: Lessons Learned from Ms. Foundation for Women Grantmaking, 2008 (Box 18, Folder 197)
  - Anna Wadia - Quality Employment Foundation Administered Project (FAP), 2010 (Box 18, Folder 198)
  - Anna Wadia - Labor Project for Working Families (LPWF), 2010 (Box 18, Folder 199)
  - Anna Wadia - Paid sick days messaging, 2009-2010 (Box 18, Folder 200)
  - Anna Wadia, 2009-2010 (Box 18, Folder 201)
  - Anna Wadia - Job quality communications, 2006-2010 (Box 18, Folder 202)
  - Chauncy Lennon, 2009-2010 (Box 18, Folder 203)